Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series III. Director Files, 1966-2006; 22 Linear Feet in 22 containers.; 579.30 Megabytes in 51 computer files.
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Program, 1972; cuid16624 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - M.A. Program in Black Studies, 1972; cuid16625 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Mathematical Sciences -- List of Departmental Chairpersons, 1972; cuid16626 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty & Administration, 1972; cuid16627 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Proposals for Funding of Research Projects, 1972; cuid16628 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Research Project -- Community College, Black Studies Instructors, 1972; cuid16629 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Sojourner Newspaper, 1972; cuid16630 (Box 121, Folder 17-18)
  - Sports Foundation, 1972; cuid16632 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1972; cuid16633 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - Wooden's John, Success Project, 1972; cuid16634 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1972; cuid16635 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - IAAA Newsletter, 1972; cuid16636 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Black Creation Magazine, 1973; cuid16637 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Black Films, 1973; cuid16638 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Black Literary, 1973; cuid16639 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Level Black Studies Courses, 1973; cuid16640 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Black Student Service Center Proposal, 1973; cuid16641 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence of Roscoe C. Brown, 1973; cuid16642 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Dilemmas of Afro-Americans Course -- Dr. Eugene Callender, 1973; cuid16643 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1973; cuid16644 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1973; cuid16645 (Box 122, Folder 12-14)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1973; cuid16648 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - IAAA Project -- Instructional Strategies and the Development of Political Thinking Among Emerging Adolescents, 1973; cuid16649 (Box 122, Folder 16-17)
  - IAAA Staff Correspondence, 1973; cuid16651 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - The Institute of the Black World: Monthly Report, 1973; cuid16652 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Journalism Council: Job and Scholarship Referral Bulletin for Minorities, 1973; cuid16653 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduate Certificates, 1973; cuid16654 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduate Reception, 1973; cuid16655 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial Program, 1973; cuid16656 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty and Administrators, 1973; cuid16657 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - NYU Staff Publication, 1973; cuid16658 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - The New York Urban Coalition, 1973; cuid16659 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1974; cuid16660 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1974; cuid16661 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1974; cuid16662 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Black Studies Programs, 1974; cuid16663 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1974; cuid16664 (Box 22, Folder 5-8)
  - IAAA Annual Report -- Draft, 1974; cuid16668 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1974; cuid16669 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - IAAA Mainstream: Radio Production and Show, 1974; cuid16670 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Newsletter: "Notes", 1974; cuid16671 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Program Planning, 1974; cuid16672 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - IAAA Proposal: Evaluation of Title I and Title VII Program, 1974; cuid16673 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Journalism Council, Inc., 1974; cuid16674 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Fourth Annual Memorial Services, 1974; cuid16675 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduate Certificates, 1974; cuid16676 (Box 22, Folder 17-19)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Reception for Graduates, 1974; cuid16679 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Minority Graduate Student Locater Service, 1974; cuid16681 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - NYU Report Biweekly Journal, 1974; cuid16682 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Robinson, Jackie Management Corp., 1974; cuid16683 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Walker, Dr. Leroy (NYU Alumnus), 1974; cuid16684 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Washington Square News, 1974; cuid16685 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1975; cuid16686 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Black Creation Magazine Copyrights, 1975; cuid16687 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Black Films, 1975; cuid16688 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Blacks in Higher Education Articles, 1975; cuid16689 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1975; cuid16690 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence of Roscoe C. Brown, 1975; cuid16691 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Advisory, 1975; cuid16692 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1975; cuid16693 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1975; cuid16694 (Box 22, Folder 35-38)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1975; cuid16698 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - IAAA Mainstream: WNYU Radio Show, 1975; cuid16699 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Planning, 1975; cuid16700 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - The Institute of the Black World: Monthly Report, 1975; cuid16701 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Journalism Council, Inc., 1975; cuid16702 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduate Certificates, 1975; cuid16703 (Box 22, Folder 44-48)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduate Reception, 1975; cuid16708 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Program -- Memorial, 1975; cuid16710 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - NYU Report Biweekly Journal, 1975; cuid16711 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Proposal Writing Workshop, 1975; cuid16712 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Still Here Magazone, 1975; cuid16713 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence -- Wyletta Barbee, 1975; cuid16714 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1975; cuid16715 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Art Collection -- Grey Art Gallery, 1975; cuid16716 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1975; cuid16717 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Bicentennial Celebration -- IAAA at NYU, 1976; cuid16718 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Black Films, William Greaves, 1976; cuid16719 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Black Genealogy Book Compilation, 1976; cuid16720 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1977; cuid16721 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series, 1976; cuid16723 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Baraka, Amiri, 1976; cuid16724 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Booth, Judge W., 1976; cuid16725 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Coombs, Ode, 1976; cuid16726 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Higgins, Jr., Chester, 1976; cuid16727 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Tolliver, Melba, 1976; cuid16728 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1976; cuid16731 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Ebony Patriots Magazone, 1976; cuid16732 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1976; cuid16735 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - IAAA Inventory, 1976; cuid16736 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - IAAA Program Planning, 1976; cuid16737 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - IAAA Summary of the Activities of the Institute of Afro-American Affairs, 1976; cuid16738 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - IAAA Seminar -- "20th Century Black Radicalism", 1976; cuid16740 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - IAAA Staff Correspondence, 1976; cuid16741 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - "Institutional Racism: Implications for Social Workers", 1976; cuid16742 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Journalism Articles and Guide -- Directory, 1976; cuid16743 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduate Certificates, 1976; cuid16744 (Box 23, Folder 24-28)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. -- Memorial, 1976; cuid16749 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Leadbelly Screening and Chronology, 1976; cuid16750 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - The Little Black Book Magazine, 1976; cuid16751 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - New York University Report Newspaper, 1976; cuid16752 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Sports Foundation, Inc., 1976; cuid16754 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Still Here Magazine, 1976; cuid16755 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Survey of Undergraduate Black Studies Courses at NYU, 1976; cuid16756 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1977; cuid16757 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1977; cuid16758 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series, 1976-1977; cuid16759 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Gil Noble, 1977; cuid16761 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: John O. Killens, 1977; cuid16762 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Basil Peterson, 1977; cuid16763 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Franklin Williams, 1977; cuid16764 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Mary Lou Williams, 1977; cuid16765 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1977; cuid16766 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Black Studies Research: Articles, 1969-1970; cuid16767 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Black Studies Research: Articles, 1973-1977; cuid16768 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1977; cuid16769 (Box 23, Folder 49-50)
  - IAAA Annual Report -- Proposed Plans and Programs, 1977; cuid16771 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - IAAA For Your Information, 1977; cuid16772 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduate Certificates, 1977; cuid16773 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduation Reception, 1977; cuid16774 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduation Reception and Student Responses, 1977; cuid16775 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial, 1977; cuid16776 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Literary Associations, 1977; cuid16777 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - National Conference of Artists, 1977; cuid16778 (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
  - New York University Report Newspaper, 1977; cuid16780 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - The New York Urban Coalition, 1977; cuid16781 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Police Athletic League, 1977; cuid16782 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Schomberg, Arthur A. Award Dinner at the Waldorf Astoria, 1977; cuid16783 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Sports Foundation, Inc., 1977; cuid16784 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Woodruff, Hale, 1977; cuid16785 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Black Creation Magazine, 1977; cuid16786 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1977; cuid16787 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Newsletter, 1977; cuid16788 (Box 24, Folder 13-14)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1978; cuid16790 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Afro-American Cultural Foundation, 1978; cuid16791 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1978; cuid16792 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Black Collegian Magazine, 1978; cuid16793 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series, 1978; cuid16794 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Lenox Hinds, 1978; cuid16795 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Benjamin Hooks, 1978; cuid16796 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Dr. Inez Smith Reid, 1978; cuid16797 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Ntozake Shange, 1978; cuid16798 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: John A. Williams, 1978; cuid16799 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Blacks in Higher Education Articles, 1978; cuid16800 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Cinque Gallery Board Meetings, 1978; cuid16801 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence -- Wyletta Barbee, 1978; cuid16802 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Student Reception, 1978; cuid16803 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1978; cuid16804 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1978; cuid16805 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - IAAA For Your Information, 1978; cuid16806 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Forms and Responses, 1978; cuid16807 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Inventory, 1978; cuid16808 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Newsbrief, 1978; cuid16809 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Program Assistant, 1978; cuid16810 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Space Inventory, 1978; cuid16811 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - IAAA Staff Projects and Activities, 1978; cuid16812 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - The Little Black Book Magazine, 1978; cuid16813 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Bibliographical Outline, 1978; cuid16814 (Box 24, Folder 39-40)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Association -- First Annual Awards Dinner, 1978; cuid16816 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduate Certificates, 1978; cuid16817 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduation Reception, 1978; cuid16818 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial, 1978; cuid16819 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Scholarship Fund, 1978; cuid16820 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - New York University Report Publication, 1978; cuid16821 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - The New York Urban Coalition, 1978; cuid16822 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Second International Congress on Education, 1978; cuid16823 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence -- Dr. Edward M. Carroll, 1978; cuid16824 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - ABFA Minority Student Achievement Award Recipients, 1979; cuid16825 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - ABFA Minority Student Achievement Award Recipients, Correspondence, 1979; cuid16826 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1979; cuid16827 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Afro-American Studies Program, 1979; cuid16828 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Black History Month Planning, 1979; cuid16829 (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
  - Black Literature, 1979; cuid16831 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Black Religion, News Articles, 1979; cuid16832 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Correspondence and General Information, 1979; cuid16833 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Dr. John Henrik Clarke, 1979; cuid16834 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Dr. Edyth J. Gaines, 1979; cuid16835 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Dr. Jeanne Noble, 1979; cuid16836 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Gordon Parks, 1979; cuid16837 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: James Steele, 1979; cuid16838 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Black Studies Programs in the U.S., 1979; cuid16839 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1979; cuid16840 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Cinque Gallery Board Meetings, 1979; cuid16841 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence of Edward M. Carroll, 1979; cuid16842 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence of Earl S. Davis, 1979; cuid16843 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Fundraising, IAAA, 1979; cuid16844 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Student Reception, 1979; cuid16845 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1979; cuid16846 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1979; cuid16847 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - IAAA Black Student Organization Steering Committee Meeting, 1979; cuid16848 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - IAAA Brochure, 1979; cuid16849 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - IAAA Program Planning, 1979; cuid16850 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - IAAA Questionnaire -- Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Material Packet, 1979; cuid16851 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Graduate Reception, 1979; cuid16852 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial Ceremony, 1979; cuid16853 (Box 25, Folder 29-31)
  - Monograph Series, Volume I, Number I, 1979; cuid16856 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Renwick Reception, 1979; cuid16857 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Research -- Enrollment and Black Studies Courses Offered at NYU, 1979; cuid16858 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Secretarial Recruitment, 1979; cuid16859 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Washington Square News, 1979; cuid16860 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - ABFA Constitution, 1980; cuid16861 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Afro-American Courses and Related Subjects Listing, 1980; cuid16862 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Benin Exhibition Correspondence, 1980; cuid16863 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: General Correspondence, 1980; cuid16864 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "Economic Development in the Black Community: 'What Will the 80's Bring?'" by Arthur H. Barnes, 1980; cuid16865 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "The Black Image in the Media" by David Lampel, 1980; cuid16866 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "Metamorphosis-Poetry Reading" Featuring Quincy Troupe, Fred Nelson, Regina Williams, Mariah Britton Howard, Wayne Providence, Cathering Sanders, 1980; cuid16867 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "The 80's -- Which Way for Black America," Guest Speaker Congressman Charles B. Rangel, 1980; cuid16868 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - BSSC, 1980; cuid16869 (Box 25, Folder 45-46)
  - Black Studies Programs Research, 1980; cuid16871 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Citicorp and NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1980; cuid16872 (Box 25, Folder 48-50)
  - Correspondence of Earl S. Davis, 1980; cuid16875 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- Louise Dennis, 1980; cuid16876 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Emerging African Nations" Correspondence -- Ambassadors and Conference, 1980; cuid16877 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Emerging African Nations" -- Forms, 1980; cuid16878 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Emerging African Nations" -- List of African Ambassadors, 1980; cuid16879 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "Emerging African Nations" -- Program Operations, 1980; cuid16880 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, 1980; cuid16881 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1980; cuid16882 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - IAAA Inventory, 1980; cuid16883 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - IAAA Lecturer and Speakers, 1980; cuid16884 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - IAAA Minority Advisory Council, 1980; cuid16885 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Staff Meetings, 1980; cuid16886 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Jazz Seminars, 1980; cuid16887 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Association, 1980; cuid16888 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial Ceremony, 1980; cuid16889 (Box 26, Folder 15-17)
  - Citicorp and NYU Business Career Forum -- Forms, 1980; cuid16892 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Citicorp and NYU Business Career Forum -- Correspondence, 1980; cuid16893 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - IAAA For Your Information, 1980; cuid16894 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Leadership Workshop -- Minority Advisory Council (MAC), 1980; cuid16895 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Minority Student Award, 1980; cuid16896 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Minority Student Recruitment at NYU, 1980; cuid16897 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - The NY Urban Coalition, 1980; cuid16898 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Organization of Black Women (OBW), 1980; cuid16899 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Orientation -- NYU, 1980; cuid16900 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Secretarial Recruitment, 1980; cuid16901 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - A Social Worker's Critique of the Afro-American Experience by Mary Hall, 1980; cuid16902 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Survey of Black Studies Courses Offered Throughout the University and Summary, 1970-1980; cuid16903 (Box 26, Folder 29-34)
  - ABFA Correspondence, 1981; cuid16909 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - ABFA Minutes of Meetings, 1981; cuid16910 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1981; cuid16911 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series -- Correspondence, 1981; cuid16912 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series -- Questionnaire, 1981; cuid16913 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Thomas S. Jacobs, "Criminal Justice System", 1981; cuid16914 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Michelle Wallace, "Black Macho and the Myth of the Superwoman", 1981; cuid16915 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Black Student Organizations at NYU, 1981; cuid16916 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1981; cuid16917 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Citicorp and NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1981; cuid16918 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence of Earl S. Davis, 1981; cuid16919 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Fundraising, 1981; cuid16920 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Girls Town, 1981; cuid16921 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1981; cuid16922 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - IAAA Advisory Board, 1981; cuid16923 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Advisory Council, 1981; cuid16924 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1981; cuid16925 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - IAAA Black Choir, 1981; cuid16926 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - IAAA For Your Information, 1981; cuid16927 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - IAAA Minority Advisory Council, 1981; cuid16928 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - IAAA Office Move, 1981; cuid16929 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - Minority Student Association Correspondence, 1981; cuid16931 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Monograph Series, 1981; cuid16932 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - UNESCO, 1981; cuid16933 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Sylvia "KUUMBA": Blacks in Theatre, 1981; cuid16934 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Benin Exhibition Catalog Publicity, 1982; cuid16935 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - "Black Theatre Forum: A Total Perspective" Questionnaires RESTRICTED, 1982; cuid16936 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Interracial Council of New York, 1982; cuid16937 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence of Earl S. Davis, 1982; cuid16938 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Funding Resources, 1982; cuid16939 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1982; cuid16940 (Box 27, Folder 12-15)
  - IAAA Brochure, 1982; cuid16944 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - IAAA Library Books Receipts, 1982; cuid16945 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - The International Law Review of Developing Nations (ILRDN) Journal Proposal, 1982; cuid16946 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - National Urban League, Inc. Disease Prevention and Health Promotion in Urban Black Communities Project Advisory Committee, 1982; cuid16947 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases of IAAA Events, 1982; cuid16948 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Reservations, IAAA, 1982; cuid16949 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - UNESCO, 1982; cuid16950 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Black Student Organizations at NYU, 1982; cuid16951 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - African American Book Resources and Listing, 1980-1983; cuid16952 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Black Politics: Compilation of Articles, 1972-1983; cuid16953 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Black Social Workers Research, 1983; cuid16954 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Black Student Organizations, 1983; cuid16955 (Box 27, Folder 27-28)
  - Black Studies and Related Courses, 1983; cuid16957 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Burrows, Vinnie -- Profile, 1983; cuid16958 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Community Groups and Organizations, 1983; cuid16959 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence of Earl S. Davis, 1983; cuid16960 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Film, Television and Art, 1983; cuid16961 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Funding Resources, 1983; cuid16963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Higher Education Opportunities Program (HEOP) Background Information, 1983; cuid16964 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1983; cuid16965 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - News Articles Sports-Related, 1983; cuid16966 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - NYU Photographs, 1983; cuid16967 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Petty Cash Vouchers and Receipts, 1983; cuid16968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Purchasing, 1983; cuid16969 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Research on Afro-American Adult Development "Journey Through Transitions" Questionnaire, 1983; cuid16970 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Transfiguration Lutheran Church, 1983; cuid16971 (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
  - UNESCO, 1983; cuid16973 (Box 28, Folder 13-14)
  - American Committee on Africa, 1984; cuid16975 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Black Lifestyles Course and School of Social Work, 1984; cuid16976 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Brown Plus Thirty Conference Sponsored by Metro Center, 1984; cuid16977 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Citicorp and NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1984; cuid16978 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Community Groups and Organizations, 1984; cuid16979 (Box 28, Folder 19)